Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Additional Files 6069
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Additional Files
1907-2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees (NUHHCE)
Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union
6069
2.5 cubic feet
2.5 linear ft.
Records.
5791204
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 11, 2008
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 23, 2016
Scope and Contents
Collection conisists of 5 albums (2 titles) have been added to the record collection labeled 6069. 1- District 1199: Bread and Roses Project Presents Take Care A Musical Revue of Life in the Hospitals. 1980; 2- 1199 25: The Union Democracy Built (a dramatic-musicall production based on highlights in the history of Local 1199)
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5929 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 5929 MB: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia 5929 P: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Photographs 6069: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Additional Files 6084 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Women of Hope Poster Sets 6085 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project "Frederick Douglass and His Time" Posters 6089 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Posters 6140: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project 6140 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio Recordings 6169 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 6169 MB: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia 6169 P: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Photographs
Bread and Roses Cultural Project; National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees; National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199
5791204
- Belafonte, Harry. "My Turn" (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Committee for Justice to Hospital Workers. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  General.
- Davis, Leon. Memorial., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Dee, Ruby. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Dubin, Marshall. "The 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Program." (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Financial Files., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Foner, Moe. Correspondence. Personal. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Foner, Moe. Bread and Roses Essays. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Foner, Moe. Notes. (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Ford Foundation Grant., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Godoff, Elliot. Memorial., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 1, Folder 13)
- National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Correspondence.
- National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Grant Proposal.
- National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- New York City. (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Publicity. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Catalogs.
- Publicity. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Flyer; Advertisments.
- Publicity. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Press Releases.
- Red Squad Documents. (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Sweden. (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Trades Union Congress. (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Vietnam. (Box 1, Folder 26)
- "Disarming Images." (Box 1, Folder 27)
- "Images of Labor." Correspondence. (Box 1, Folder 28)
- "Images of Labor." General. (Folder 1). (Box 1, Folder 29)
  General. (Folder 1).
- "Images of Labor." General. (Folder 2). (Box 1, Folder 30)
  General. (Folder 2).
- "Images of Labor." Seattle. (Box 1, Folder 31)
- "Not Bread Alone." (Box 1, Folder 32)
- "Take Care." General. (Box 1, Folder 33)
- "Take Care." Scripts. (Box 1, Folder 34)
- "Take Care." Sellner, Judith B. Essays. (Box 1, Folder 35)
- "Women of Hope." (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Clippings., 1950-1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Clippings., 1960-1970 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Clippings., 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Clippings., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Contract Campaign.
- Clippings., 1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Clippings., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Clippings., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Clippings., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Clippings., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Clippings., 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Clippings., 1990-2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Clippings. (Box 2, Folder 12)
- For the Union Makes Us Strong., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Images of Labor, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Hardcover
- Images of Labor, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Paperback
- Leon J. Davis: Founder of 1199, 1907-1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Bread and Roses: A Special Report. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Everything's Coming Up Bread and Roses: A Progress Report. (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Our Own Show: Organizing Cultural Programs for Working People. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Portraits Of and By 1199 Retired Members. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- 1199 Drug News., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  v.32:no.3 (1965:Mar.)
- 1199 Drug News., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  v.32:no.6 (1965:June)
- 1199 Drug & Hospital News., 1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  v.4:no.3 (1969:Mar.)
- 1199 Drug & Hospital News., 1970 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  v.5:no.4 (1970:Apr.)
- 1199 Drug & Hospital News., 1970 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  v.5:no.7 (1970:July)
- 1199 Drug & Hospital News., 1968 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  v.3:no.10 (1968:Dec.)
- 1199 News., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  v.16:no.5 (1981:May)
- 1199 News., 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  v.19:no.7 (1984:Aug./Sept.)
- 1199 News., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  v.16:no.3 (1981:Mar.)
- 1199 News., 1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  v.15:no.1 (1980:Jan.)
- 1199 News., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  v.14:no.4 (1979:Apr.)
- 1199 News., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  v.14:no.3 (1979:Mar.)
- 1199 News., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  v.14:no.2 (1979:Feb.)
- 1199 News., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  v.14:no.1 (1979:Jan.)
- 1199 News., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  v.10:no.3 (1975:Mar.)
- 1199 News., 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  v.13:no.12 (1995:Dec.)
- Local 1199 Hospital News. v.1:no.4(1959:Feb.26) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  (1959:Feb.26)
- Meet Your Union: A Booklet for New Members. Local 5. (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Meet Your Union: A Booklet for New Members. Local 1250. (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Working in Department Stores: Yesterday, Today, and Tomorrow. United Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees of America, CIO., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- 5 for 5. Local 5., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- The Origins of Left Culture in the U.S.: 1880-1940., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Annual Review: The Equitable Foundation., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Hereies #15. "Racism Is The Issue.", 1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Local 535: 30 Years. Wow., 1993 (Box 3, Folder 15)